{
  "name": "Maths times tables 5 to 8",
  "uniqueid": "8488c660-5b34-4147-a955-ece4bc77fdae",
  "enabled": true,
  "questions": [
    {
      "questionText": "5 x 1",
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "5 x 2",
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "5 x 3",
      "answer": "15"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "5 x 4",
      "answer": "20"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "5 x 5",
      "answer": "25"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "5 x 6",
      "answer": "30"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "5 x 7",
      "answer": "35"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "5 x 8",
      "answer": "40"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "5 x 9",
      "answer": "45"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "5 x 10",
      "answer": "50"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "5 x 11",
      "answer": "55"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "5 x 12",
      "answer": "60"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "6 x 1",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "6 x 2",
      "answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "6 x 3",
      "answer": "18"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "6 x 4",
      "answer": "24"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "6 x 5",
      "answer": "30"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "6 x 6",
      "answer": "36"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "6 x 7",
      "answer": "42"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "6 x 8",
      "answer": "48"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "6 x 9",
      "answer": "54"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "6 x 10",
      "answer": "60"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "6 x 11",
      "answer": "66"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "6 x 12",
      "answer": "72"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "7 x 1",
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "7 x 2",
      "answer": "14"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "7 x 3",
      "answer": "21"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "7 x 4",
      "answer": "28"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "7 x 5",
      "answer": "35"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "7 x 6",
      "answer": "42"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "7 x 7",
      "answer": "49"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "7 x 8",
      "answer": "56"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "7 x 9",
      "answer": "63"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "7 x 10",
      "answer": "70"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "7 x 11",
      "answer": "77"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "7 x 12",
      "answer": "84"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "8 x 1",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "8 x 2",
      "answer": "16"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "8 x 3",
      "answer": "24"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "8 x 4",
      "answer": "32"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "8 x 5",
      "answer": "40"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "8 x 6",
      "answer": "48"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "8 x 7",
      "answer": "56"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "8 x 8",
      "answer": "64"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "8 x 9",
      "answer": "72"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "8 x 10",
      "answer": "80"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "8 x 11",
      "answer": "88"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "8 x 12",
      "answer": "96"
    }
  ],
  "rules": {
    "questionsPerGame": 10,
    "answerAlternatives": "11223344556677889900",
    "answerButtonLimit": 5
  },
  "metadata": {
    "targetAges": [
      5,
      6
    ]
  }
}